Long ago, Gold Roger,
the King of Pirates, obtained
everything the world had to offer,
and his dying roads drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
And thus a new age began.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Oh, I'm done playing
through with the waiting.
Either way, I'm feeling alive!
Look out below.
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
Raise your flag up high.
Hail a brand new dawn.
Blaze across the sky.
Time to journey on.
On your mark.
Camel of other things.
We're on Earth, a legendary.
If you can show your breath,
then we'll make some waves.
We run on daunted, ain't no beginners.
Cause if you're wanted,
then you're a winner.
For we are on the cruise.
And freedom is the only rule.
Fearless night and day.
Cause that's just our way.
Find one piece, I'll be the first.
I'll put it, be so bad, just be first.
It's all this real.
It must be cause my hand's on a wheel.
I'm done playing, filled with the waiting.
In a world I'm feeling
alive, but I'll be loud.
Wake up, sunshine, here we go.
We have come so far.
Gotta make it to the end.
Whatever danger we find,
no one ever left behind.
I've always got your back, my friend.
Sail on shoreward, keep marching forward.
Dreaming from the very
first day I'd make my name.
And don't you know that
dream hasn't changed.
I'm done playing through with the wave.
In every world I'm feeling alive.
Look out below.
Wake up, sunshine.
Wake up, sunshine. I'm here!
We go!
Hold on, Luffy, what are you doing? Stop!
Megalo, come back here now!
Stay in the palace!
Father, brothers, all my
caretakers, forgive me.
I'm leaving without your permission.
I promise to be home by dinner!
We're on an adventure!
What has gotten into Megalo?
I can't believe it, he
even left the doors open!
What if something were to happen to...
Oh no!
Hey, Skeleton!
Hurry up and check on the princess!
Alright, stop writing my bones about it!
She's gone!
Princess Shirahoshi never leaves her room!
Oh no!
But why are you keeping her
locked up here in the first place?
To keep her safe!
Enemies are trying to get to her!
Kidnap you!
I'm sorry I failed you!
Who knows how far away the kidnappers are!
Kidnappers?
Princess Shirahoshi!
Forgive me!
You're positive she was kidnapped?
How rude of you!
The gate connecting Fishman
Island to the Ryugu Palace.
Tell us where the switch
to open it is or else.
Wait, switch?
Skeleton, you have to get back to
King Nephew as fast as possible.
Tell him the princess is gone
and that we're under attack.
We didn't want any of this to
happen, but it's the only way.
They told us that if we want to survive,
we've got to follow their orders.
Please just tell us okay who's orders
it doesn't matter just tell us or
we're all gonna die I don't Just tell
us what in the world is going on here
You pirates are now under the control
of Horny Jones so listen closely
I've got wonderful You have the chance
to be part of a historic mission!
Talk about lucky!
That looks like Van Der Decken.
Isn't he the captain
of the Flying Dutchman?
This can't be real!
That cursed ghost ship is a myth!
Oh, I'm no ghost, but I am
Van Der Decken's descendant!
I've got a curse of my own as well.
Even though I'm a fishman, I can't swim!
But that's all right!
I've got this Devil Fruit power
known as the Markmark fruit!
How about I show you you and
the stripes come here step right up me
yeah
this
is nonsense and
you know it enough is enough?
Is that Hachi?
What is he doing here?
Hello there.
Those energy steroids you're taking
will do nothing but mess up your body.
And no good can come of
destroying Fishman Island.
On top of it, you're underestimating
the power of Neptune.
Hachi, I've heard enough of your rambling.
I don't want to listen
to your voice anymore.
To think you were an officer of
the pirate group that I admired.
Now you're nothing but a washed-up coward.
So, make way for the real pirates.
If we want to teach all of the humans a
lesson, we're gonna need Fishman Island.
That means Neptune is our enemy.
Arlong thought Fishmen
were the supreme race.
When did you change your mind?
Arlong was wrong.
There is no supreme race.
Deacon? Yasuie?
Why are you doing this?
The two of you refused to help Arlong
invade the East Blue when he was in power.
So tell me, what makes you want to
work with these young punks now?
That's easy.
I meant it for money.
These guys are willing to pay.
Arlong was stingy.
He never did pony up enough
dough to enlist my services.
That's why he was always stuck taking
crappy swordsmen like you along.
No wonder he lost.
A sight for sore eyes.
An angry Hachi.
Yeah, I remember what happened back then.
Arlong had the nerve to ask
me to work underneath him.
What a preposterous idea.
Van Der Decken never works under anybody.
I'm my own man.
Heart gets that better than anyone.
Arlong had goals and an ability to
act on them, which I can respect.
But he was also brash.
As a leader, he was lacking and cunning.
When you old-timers were
running rampant on the sea,
we were all still too young to
become pirates, so we watched.
We saw what you did well
and what you did poorly.
We learned from all your mistakes.
In that sense, we owe you our thanks.
Take heart.
I will continue right
where Arlong left off.
I don't understand why you're
not on board with that.
You've supported Arlong for
all those years, after all.
What a disappointment you are, Hachi.
You might want to know.
The pirate who destroyed Arlong's dream,
Straw Hat Luffy, is on Fishman Island.
It's a perfect opportunity
for some revenge.
Even though I fought him as a
member of the Arlong Pirates,
he now calls me his friend. Look!
All three of you are my friends now!
Straw Hat Luffy also saved my life.
If I could, I would see him.
But I'm too ashamed of my
fellow fishmen to do it.
How can I face him when you're
clinging to Arlong's legacy?
You consider a human your friend?
How pathetic.
You're not a real fishman.
Get out of my sight.
Calm yourself and listen.
You may have forgotten
how pirates do things
around here if there's
something you want to say.
You gotta use violence
to get your point across.
For example, what where
is he throwing it to did?
You notice when I touched you earlier
I marked you as my new target.
No matter what I throw
or where I throw it,
it will always make its way
back to whatever I mark.
Not only that, but it'll
come back at you full speed.
I suspect that's crazy.
Decking just tossed the knife away from
that guy and it came back to hit him.
The mark. Mark.
Curse of course.
There are some limitations.
Can you figure them out?
You had better hurry.
Stay away from me. Decking.
I've heard enough stories
about your mark mark power.
You gotta make him stop.
He's trying to kill me.
Please stop him. Horny.
Sorry, Hachi.
I can't.
As he told you earlier,
Vanderdecken isn't working under me.
We're allies on equal footing.
Besides, you're really
starting to get on my nerves.
Go ahead, Decken.
Dammit!
Alright!
Fall!
That's it! Run away!
No matter how fast you run.
Or how far you go,
they'll keep chasing you until
they meet their mark, and you know?
what that means!
I'll be okay if I can just
find my way to the exit!
There, I should be safe now.
Hopefully they sink in the water.
They burst on the bubble like
it was nothing! Get away!
I can leave up to two marks, one
for each palm, left and right.
But I've worn a glove on
this one for ten years.
Since I touched Princess
Shirahoshi and made her my mark,
she'll stay that way forever.
Get it yet?
I can throw weapons and even my love,
they'll track you down to
the furthest depths of hell.
That's the mark mark curse for you.
Whoa!
He can keep stalking the
princess for as long as he wants!
And stay right here!
Best of all, he'll never have to deal
with fighting Neptune and his sons!
Bingo!
How devious can you get?
Now, about you human pirates.
I'm sure you're all familiar
with Deccan's mark mark power.
So, let's begin the first
stage of your mission.
They say the Ryugu Palace is
impregnable, but I disagree.
Someone in this room
has been able to break
through its defenses
for ten straight years.
Him, Captain Vander Decken.
So,
you'll be our cannon fodder,
meaning Decken will treat your
bodies as living ammunition.
Throwing you straight into the
wall of the princess's tower.
Of course weapons can't smash it and
most of you runts won't do any better.
And then you'll open up the
gate from inside the palace,
find the gate switch and let us in.
That's all you have to do.
Wait, we can't make it that far.
You're crazy.
We'd already be dead.
From hitting the wall.
You're correct.
That's why I want you humans to do it.
Your lives don't mean anything to me.
In our world you're
either slaves or corpses.
Those of you who survived the
impact carry out your duty.
If you succeed in opening
the gate I'll set you free.
But if you refuse to do it then leave.
I'll get you out of the bubble myself.
So you better do as I say.
But if if we leave the? bubble?
We can't get to the top without drowning.
Well, that's no good.
On the upside, that should
make this decision easy for you though.
Have fun!
It's a new era.
From now on, our people
will forge a new history
with our own hands.
We'll start by conquering
the Ryugu Kingdom.
Shura Hachi, just you wait!
Meanwhile, back at the palace.
Don't go so fast! We're injured!
Pick up the pace, skeleton!
It's imperative we make it to the king!
Listen, I'm begging you
to take us to that gate!
Party's gonna kill us all
if we don't get it open!
You have to!
It can't happen!
Hey, Sanji!
Don't fight them, we gotta run!
Or whatever.
Eat them all up. Sure.
Did you realize we were
innocent before you did that?
Well, it's their fault
for trying to handcuff me.
Look at what you've done!
Now everybody's giving
us that dead fish stare,
and not because they're fishmen either!
That's not our problem.
Besides, they saw the guards attack us.
But you were the one
doing all the attacking!
Hey, now, you beat up a lot of them, too.
Speaking of, good job.
Your training really paid off.
You think you can buy me
off with a compliment?
No way, pal.
The lady is in need!
Oh, my God, there's a man
covered with blood on the shore!
That guy from the Fishman District!
What happened to you?
Someone call a doctor!
Oh, hey, I'm a doctor!
What? Hachi?
Who did this? What happened?
Hachi, it's us!
Chopper and Sanji!
Hold on, we'll help you!
Why would someone do this?
It's you guys!
I'm happy to see you!
Is Straw Hat here too?
He's not with us!
Don't try to move!
I'll start treating you in a sec!
Wherever your friends are, find
them and get the hell out of here.
You don't want to get
involved, believe me.
Get back on your boat and leave
this place while you still can,
or you'll be fighting for your lives.
Hordeon, Deccan, go.
The new fishman pirates will start
attacking the whole island soon.
But once they do, the
Ryugu kingdom will fall.
King Neptune!
the princess has been kidnapped
i don't know how but they must
have broken into the room also
pirates are crashing into the tower
it's bizarre in any case they'll
be here any minute get ready
kidnapped somebody's taken away my
Shirahoshi who was it i'll kill them
wait there's a pirate
raid going on and they
don't mean this is the
worst time all i want is get
out of here and now
it's some kind of pirate
party we're screwed fine
just ignore me jerk i'll
cut him violence is the
last thing we need right
now if we want to make
it out of here alive we
have to open up the gates
no matter what oh no
they're here you can come
out of the shark now you
Oh, that's okay.
I think I'd rather stay inside for now.
Must be nice after being
cooped up for ten years.
Yes, my heart is racing.
They're probably worried sick about me.
You've been out five minutes.
Have a little fun, would ya?
Jeez, what a weirdo.
Now I know how it feels.
This is a real adventure, huh?
It sure is!
If your heart's racing,
it counts as an adventure!
You mentioned a thing
called a sea forest, right?
So what is that?
Is it a pretty cool place?
It's a graveyard.
Or rather, there's one grave that I never
got to visit because I was locked away.
Ten years I've wanted to go, and now
my only dream can finally come true!
It's already been ten long
years since her assassination
in broad daylight proved
Fishman Island into upheaval.
Time flies.
The princes have grown into
strong and worthy protectors.
Princess Shirahoshi is locked
in the tower, but she is safe.
But as for you, your memory survives.
Your ideals will live on forever.